{
    "id": "60c6add3f2424059bc2ab75795626330",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. he is honest, nobody trusts him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you tell me the truth, I will call the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Until",
                "Unless",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not as clever …………………. his younger brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be punished …………………. he is guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He will be punished ……………….. he is found guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Give every man thy ear, ……………… few thy voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He will die someday ………………… all men are mortal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "like",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard, ………………… he might pass the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "as",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for him …………………. 11 pm, but he didn’t come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "upto",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the prize …………………. you deserve it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "until",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been an year ……………….. I saw him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did he see the tiger ………………. he fainted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly had we reached the platform ……………. the train arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}